Part dog. Part man. All hero.
Dog Man is a family, comedy, adventure film directed by Peter Hastings.
When a faithful police dog and his human police officer owner are injured together on the job, a
harebrained but life-saving surgery fuses the two of them together and Dog Man is born.
Dog Man is sworn to protect and serve—and fetch, sit and roll over.
As Dog Man embraces his new identity and strives to impress his Chief, he must
stop the pretty evil plots of feline supervillain Petey the Cat.
Dog Man / Officer Knight / Harold's House (voice), played by Peter Hastings.
Petey the Cat (voice), played by Pete Davidson.
Chief (voice), played by Lil Rel Howery.
Sarah Hatoff (voice), played by Isla Fisher.
Li'l Petey (voice), played by Lucas Hopkins Calderon.
Flippy (voice), played by Ricky Gervais.
Dog Man is a 2025 American animated superhero comedy film produced by DreamWorks
Animation and based on the children's graphic novel series by Dav Pilkey.
It is a spin-off to Captain Underpants: The First Epic Movie (2017) and
the second film in the Captain Underpants franchise.
The film was written and directed by Peter Hastings, and stars the voices of Pete Davidson, Lil Rel Howery, Isla Fisher,
Lucas Hopkins Calderon, and Ricky Gervais, with Hastings providing vocal effects for the titular character.
DreamWorks Animation announced a film adaptation of Dog Man in December 2020, with Hastings set to write and
direct after his experience with Pilkey's works from The Epic Tales of Captain Underpants (2018–20).
Karen Foster joined as a producer in January 2024, and
the cast was announced that September.
Dog Man premiered at the 2025 Festival de l'Alpe d'Huez in Alpe d'Huez, France on January 15, 2025,
and was theatrically released in the United States on January 31 by Universal Pictures.
The film received positive reviews from critics and grossed
$145.6 million worldwide on a $40 million budget.
The film explores themes of villain, based on children's
book, spin off, police dog, human animal hybrid.
The tone is lighthearted.